Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: Nov 8, 2022

Flask LLP ("us", "we", or "our") operates the Zones iOS/watchOS application ("this app").

By using this app, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

1\. Information Collection And Use
----------------------------------

### 1-1. Health Data

We will use Apple's APIs to read and/or write certain data to the Apple Health app on your device (the “Health Data”). Such information may include, for example:

* Workouts
* Heart Rate
* Distance
* Active Energy

We will use your Health Data to show you the workout details and judge the heart rate zones.

We will not use your Health Data for marketing or advertising purposes. Your Health Data will be accessed locally through the Apple Health and will not be stored or cached by the app. Your Health Data will not be sent to our server. This app cannot read from or write to the Apple Health without your consent.

### 1-2. Location Data

This app will be able to access location data from sources such as GPS, Wi-Fi and cell towers once you consent to track your location (the “Location Data”).

We will not use your Location Data for marketing or advertising purposes. This app cannot read your location without your consent. You can change your mobile device settings by following the instructions [here](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT203033).

#### Purpose of Use

##### Recording of route maps

When you use this app to measure outdoor workouts, your Location Data is stored in Apple Health. Your Location Data will be accessed locally through Apple Health and will not be stored or cached by the app.

##### Adding weather information

If you use the ability to add weather information to your workout, this app sends your Location Data to [Apple Weather](https://developer.apple.com/weatherkit/) to retrieve weather information. This feature is disabled by default and can be enabled with your consent.

2\. Security
------------

The security of your information is important to us, but remember that no method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

3\. Changes To This Privacy Policy
----------------------------------

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

We will not change this agreement to allow the collection of your personal information or make other significant changes without your consent.

4\. Disclaimers
---------------

We make no guarantees as to the suitability of this app for the user, or for any of its functionality, product price, accuracy, or usefulness, and will not be held responsible in the event that damage is incurred.

We reserve the right to change this app or to stop offering it. This company will not be held responsible if this app is discontinued, changed, or otherwise made unusable and data is damaged or lost as a result, or if the device itself is damaged, or if the device incurred damage due to another app.

5\. Contact Us
--------------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

Flask LLP  
support@flaskapp.com
